<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Forums / Multimedia and Games]]></title>
    <link rel="self" href="https://bbs.archlinux.org/extern.php?action=feed&amp;fid=32&amp;type=atom"/>
    <link href="https://bbs.archlinux.org/index.php"/>
    <updated>2025-08-29T17:29:55Z</updated>
    <generator>FluxBB</generator>
    <id>https://bbs.archlinux.org/index.php</id>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Solved] WINE does not start at all]]></title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://bbs.archlinux.org/viewtopic.php?id=307811&amp;action=new"/>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="quotebox"><cite>seth wrote:</cite><blockquote><div><p>It is also an awesome way to trash/invalidate/outdate your local database, so don&#039;t.<br />Also please avoid bloating the thread w/ pointless full quotes (which is about me having to scroll more <img src="https://bbs.archlinux.org/img/smilies/tongue.png" width="15" height="15" alt="tongue" />)</p></div></blockquote></div><p>Ah I see. Thanks for the info!~</p><p>Anyways, back to the topic at hand:</p><div class="quotebox"><cite>seth wrote:</cite><blockquote><div><p>1. is this still wine-stable or actully wine from the repos</p></div></blockquote></div><p>This is still wine-stable. I didn&#039;t want to use the one from the repos (iirc, that is wine-staging) mainly because I didn&#039;t want to completely bork the existing configuration (as I am not the most experienced with WINE). This is the latest version of it as of yesterday.</p><div class="quotebox"><cite>seth wrote:</cite><blockquote><div><p>2. which version of medibang paint pro is this?</p></div></blockquote></div><p>I don&#039;t know. I installed this version on my Windows installation back when I used to daily drive Windows, and I do not know how I can check it when it doesn&#039;t run. AFAIK, this exact same version is the one on the laptop, so I would take a wager that something minor changed from WINE 9 to WINE 10.</p><p>I was busy today but only got back now. I didn&#039;t mention for brevity but I also tried LTSpice XVII and it didn&#039;t work due to similar error yesterday when I first started this thread. Now I have tried to run LTSpice and it works without issue (haven&#039;t tested fully yet, but it launches and that&#039;s more than it was doing yesterday).</p><p>I&#039;ve played around with LTSpice now, and no major issues to report back. Since LTSpice has loaded, I now deduce that now it is an issue with MediBangPaintPro, so I will install a newer version and report back.</p><p>I think this issue is with MediBangPaintPro itself, as I tried installing 29.1, but WINE still freaks out on launching it... I will mark this as solved since this isn&#039;t a WINE issue anymore.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name><![CDATA[nephtalima]]></name>
            <uri>https://bbs.archlinux.org/profile.php?id=171009</uri>
        </author>
        <updated>2025-08-24T23:41:54Z</updated>
        <id>https://bbs.archlinux.org/viewtopic.php?id=307811&amp;action=new</id>
    </entry>
</feed>
